suziphillips.com 2016-10-28

# Privacy

**** Totally-Traffic.com  Privacy Policy****

** Totally-Traffic.com ** ****  has established this Privacy Policy consisting of ten principles, to protect and manage your (the customer’s) personal information.  Totally-Traffic.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy.  When it does, Totally-Traffic.com will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.  For changes to this policy, Totally-Traffic.com will notify you by placing a notice on its web site home page.

Totally-Traffic.com collects, at time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) such as your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and your computer hardware and software (e.g. IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses), a listing of which can be found by clicking here.

Totally-Traffic.com has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its customers, and to respond to any inquiries and complaints.  The Privacy Policy also provides that Totally-Traffic.com will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on Totally-Traffic.com’s behalf .

Totally-Traffic.com has designated responsibility for your personal information to its Privacy Officer, who ensures compliance with the principles in this Privacy Policy.  Other Totally-Traffic.com individuals may be delegated to act on behalf of the Privacy Officer.

| ** 2.** | ** Purposes for Collecting Personal Information**  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com collects and uses personal information for the following Identified Purposes:

(a) |  to understand customer needs regarding Totally-Traffic.com’s services;  
---|---  
(b) |  to develop and provide products and services for its customers;  
---|---  
(c) |  to communicate with customers, and to inform customers of upgrades, products and services available from Totally-Traffic.com and its affiliates;  
---|---  
(d) |  to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of Totally-Traffic.com’s site;  
---|---  
(e) |  to personalize some of our services and products for you;  
---|---  
(f) |  to bill accounts and maintain payment records;  
---|---  
(g) |  to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;  
---|---  
(h) |  to respond to a legitimate claim that you are violating the rights of any third party;  
---|---  
(i) |  to protect the services, products or rights of Totally-Traffic.com; and  
---|---  
(j) |  to identify and resolve technical problems concerning Totally-Traffic.com’s products and services.  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e. not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.

If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes.

** 3.** | ** Consent for Collection, Use or Disclosure**  
---|---  
  
Registration for Totally-Traffic.com products and services by a customer will constitute the customer’s consent for Totally-Traffic.com to collect, use and disclose personal information under this Privacy Policy.  Totally-Traffic.com will normally seek a customer’s consent for any new uses and disclosures of the customer’s personal information, either at the same time it collects the personal information or after it has been collected but before it is used or disclosed for a new purpose. In certain circumstances however, Totally-Traffic.com will not be required to inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, or the collection of a debt.

A customer may withdraw such consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time, on prior written notice, provided that Totally-Traffic.com may on such withdrawal suspend or terminate its products and services.

** 4.** | ** Limiting the Collection of Personal Information**  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes.  Totally-Traffic.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children.

When you visit the Totally-Traffic.com web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the Totally-Traffic.com site previously.  Totally-Traffic.com uses cookies to allow Totally-Traffic.com to determine which products and services you have already purchased so that Totally-Traffic.com does not provide redundant information to you, and to track Totally-Traffic.com sales made to customers referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program.  If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Totally-Traffic.com web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the Totally-Traffic.com site.

** 5.** | ** Disclosure, Processing and Retention**  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else except, when the Identified Purposes require Totally-Traffic.com to disclose the personal information to:

(a) |  an agent of the customer;  
---|---  
(b) |  agents of Totally-Traffic.com acting on its behalf for the Identified Purposes;  
---|---  
(c) |  a public authority, to avoid or minimize danger to life or property; and  
---|---  
(d) |  a third party to which disclosure is required by any law, regulation, legal process or government request.  
---|---  
  
Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which Totally-Traffic.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities.  By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Totally-Traffic.com abides by the “safe harbor” framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

After your account becomes inactive, Totally-Traffic.com will keep your personal information only for those purposes which are established by law, and for archival record purposes.

** 6.** | ** Accuracy of Personal Information**  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information.  Customers are responsible for informing Totally-Traffic.com about changes to their personal information.  Totally-Traffic.com will update personal information when necessary to keep it accurate or else provide customers the facility to make such updates. 

Totally-Traffic.com will use reasonable efforts to protect personal information against loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse or modification, through security safeguards that depend on the level of sensitivity of the information.  Methods of protection include organizational measures (contract provisions, security clearance, limiting access to need-to-know Totally-Traffic.com personnel), technological measures (passwords, encryption), and physical measures (locked file storage, security card access).  Totally-Traffic.com will control personal information disclosed to authorized third parties by entering into agreements which contain confidentiality provisions and restrictions on use and which limit the amount of information disclosed to only that which is needed for the Identified Purposes.

This Privacy Policy, and all updates to the Privacy Policy made from time to time, are published and made available to Totally-Traffic.com’s customers on its web site.  It is the customer’s obligation to periodically check the Totally-Traffic.com web site for Privacy Policy updates.

** 9.** | ** Access to Personal Information**  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, in understandable format, either by direct access or upon request to the Privacy Officer made by you after providing sufficient identification.

If Totally-Traffic.com is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer’s personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney–client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.

Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, and Totally-Traffic.com will promptly correct such personal information or provide the means for you to do so directly.

** 10.** | ** Challenging Compliance**  
---|---  
  
Totally-Traffic.com wants to ensure that its Privacy Policy meets its customers’ needs.  If you feel that the Privacy Policy needs improvement, or believe that Totally-Traffic.com is not following its Privacy Policy, please contact the Privacy Officer.

Totally-Traffic.com will investigate your suggestions and complaints concerning the Totally-Traffic.com Privacy Policy. If a complaint is found to be justified, Totally-Traffic.com will take appropriate measures to resolve the complaint including, if necessary, amending its policies and procedures. Each customer will be informed of the outcome of the investigation regarding the customer’s complaint.
